

Lucas Gnutzmann

UX/UI Designer

PROFILE

I'm a UX/UI Designer studying Advertising and Propaganda. I've worked as a Graphic Designer and with Marketing in general, and I'm currently working with creation of low and high fidelity prototypes of digital products aimed at Mobile.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSIDADE PAULISTA

-Advertising and marketing Graduation 2019-2023

UDEMY

-Digital Marketing 2021

COURSERA (GOOGLE)

- -Foundations of User Experience
- -Wireframes and Low Fidelity Prototypes
- -Conduct UX research and test early concepts 2022

ESPECIALIDADE

Photoshop

Illustrator

Figma

NUMBER FOR CONTACT +55 (14) 99198-2088

EMAIL gnulucas@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO https://abre.ai/fdst

EXPERIENCE

B2R Agency

2020

Responsible for the development of digital material for the clients' social networks, as well as for offline media (Outdoor, banner).

Grupo LER

2020 - 2021

Responsible for developing digital material for clients' social networks, as well as for offline media (Outdoor, banner) and tabloids for supermarkets.

ZOOM Agency

2021

Rresponsible for customer service and development of material for their social networks, from content to graphic creation.

Lwart Ambiental Solutions

2021 - 2022

Paid internship in the area of communication and marketing, creating internal campaigns, as well as their graphic content. Assistance also in the management of comments on social networks and in the search for improvements to the company's website.

DEV12BR

2022 - 2023

UX/UI Designer, designing wireframes, low- and high-fidelity prototypes and performing market research aimed at the mobile audience.